we are bringing P solution to the market
and we are super successful in
Switzerland my passion are always to go
to International and going to us and
then spontaneously we actually go to
Orlando Direction last year and on the
very last day we joined the session from
the talent program by kurk immediately
we know that's the point there where my
American Dream comes through that we can
open a branch here in the US in the same
hour and say hey okay we have to join
this program I am happy to have a strong
partner who helps me with recruiting the
best talents for Swiss salery we're so
happy that we found our first US
employee to join our team and to make
our Dream Come
True oh it's
exciting it's super exciting um to be
the number one um in the United States
to me it will be an adventure um
Bridging the Gap between Switzerland and
the United States but I'm willing and
committed to be a part of the team I'm
at the point in my career where I'm
looking for more growth opportunities
and I feel for me the res skill program
um is providing just that I have a great
payroll background experience but the
res skill program will tap into my
technical experience with Microsoft
business Central I'm confident that I'll
be able to learn about business Central
and essentially be an expert in the
system we always talk about the need for
Bridging the Gap and and the resale
program I think gives an incentive for
Outsiders to come in learn business
Central and start at a higher level we
know we have the best product on the
market and growing the company in
Switzerland even in the United States is
the most successful key growing and
onboarding more talents in our company
so the risk kill program is the key for
our success and growing of the companies
[Music]